dotnet-tricks.com 2019-02-19

# Privacy Policy | Dot Net Tricks

We have made every effort to ensure your information is secure. We are committed to protecting your right to privacy as a user of our website. This privacy policy information covers what information is collected, what we do with it, and what you can do about it. You can use this information to make your decisions about your privacy.

### About Us

Dot Net Tricks offers corporate training, classroom training as well as instructor-led online training programs by the experienced industry mentors. With DOT NET TRICKS mentors, you can enchance your skills as per changing technology landscape. Our training programs are specially designed for that, so that your can develop your real-world application with latest technologies from start to end.

### Our Information Practices

We have tried to ensure the accuracy of the information on the website; the content is naturally subject to change. We are not responsible for any damages arising from the use of the information held on our site.

We assure that all our downloadable training contents are virus free. However, we can accept no liability for damages resulting from virus infection.

### Information collected by Us

  1. You have total control on the privacy of your information.
  2. Your information will never be sold, exchanged or disclosed to any third party for marketing purposes.
  3. You can opt to receive offers from us.

### Usage of the Website

You can browse our website without registration. We may collect and store the information that you voluntarily disclose to us, in order to access our free article, eBooks and tests. We do not share your personal information with any third party.

### Information used by Us

We may use your information to contact you via email or telephone, typically to get feedback, to inform you about new products or provide support on your issues. If you do not want us to contact you via email, you can unsubscribe at any time.

When you purchase our online products or register for a classroom training, you need to make the payment online, thus you will be required to share with us your personal information such as name, e-mail address, telephone number, address(s), credit card number, expiration, and CVV number.

During this program, we store your contact information in our registration and order-entry systems. Your credit card information is never stored in our system as it is processed by our payment gateway which uses Secure Encryption Technology (SSL). Our payment processing partners are CCAvenue, PayPal, and Google Checkout

### Cookie Information

In order to enhance your online experience and track website performance, our website uses cookies. It's a small text file which gets placed in your computer hard drive and can be retrieved later. Cookies do not tell us who you are.

To provide superior online shopping experience, our shopping cart may use cookies to temporarily store names and email addresses. Cookies will never store credit card information as they're processed using payment gateways that use Secure Encryption Technology.

### Course Content

Course content for all the study programs both online and classroom training programs, is provided only for the purpose of education and guidance. The course content is reviewed regularly and is subject to change without notice. Dot Net Tricks reserves the right to modify training content without notice.

### External Links

Our website may have links to other sites, which include third party websites or resources. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and information practices of third party websites. Please read the privacy policies of third party websites as every website has different terms of use and privacy policies.

### Copyright Information

You can electronically copy or take print outs of the website pages, only for personal use. Dot Net Tricks holds the copyright to all the material on this website, unless otherwise indicated. A written permission from the copyright holder must be obtained for any use of this material other than for purposes permitted by law.

### Personal Information Policy Image and Video Capture

Any images captured during events organized and hosted by Dot Net Tricks should not be misused which includes pictures of Dot Net Tricks staff and training participants. If you enroll in a Dot Net Tricks course your picture may also be featured in photos or videos of the Dot Net Tricks classes.

### Sharing Your Personal Information

If you have purchased a Dotnet Tricks course, we may ask you for a testimonial and with your authorization, display your testimonial, photos or videos on our website or in our social media channels such as Facebook, YouTube or Flickr. You should be aware that your publicly identifiable information could be used to send you promotional, unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for your personal information which you have chosen to display.

If you do not want us to feature your pictures/testimonials on our website or on our social media channels, you can send an email to [support@dotnettricks.com](mailto:support@dotnettricks.com)

### Personal Information Corrections

You can contact us if you notice that the information we are holding is incorrect or incomplete. Please send us an email at [support@dotnettricks.com](mailto:support@dotnettricks.com)

### Changes to Privacy Policy

These privacy policy terms may change time to time and we reserve the right to change the terms of the privacy policy at any time. When we update the privacy policy, all our registered users will be notified via email.

### Privacy Policy Questions?

If you have any questions regarding Dot Net Tricks Privacy Policy, please write to [support@dotnettricks.com](mailto:support@dotnettricks.com)
